Chukwuebuka Osuji

Frontend and Blockchain Engineer (Tailwind css, Javascript, React, Next, and Solidity) with 1 year of experience. Strong ownership mindset, proficient in frontend technologies, excellent communication and collaboration skills, and a passion for learning and adapting to new technologies.

chukwuebukaosuji@gmail.com o8136114332 <u>Linkdin profile</u> Github profile

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tekyville LLC

Frontend Engineer

USA, Miramar (Remote)

APR 2023 - DEC 2023

- Among a team of 5 tasked for the development of LogiTracer, a dynamic application designed for real-time tracking of goods.
- Leveraged Google Maps API to seamlessly integrate location tracking functionalities, providing users with an intuitive interface to monitor the movement of goods in transit.
- Collaborated closely with UX/UI design teams to enhance the visual appeal and user experience of LogiTracer, ensuring optimal usability and accessibility for all users.

Grandida LLC

Blockchain Developer

USA, Miramar (Remote)

JAN 2023 -MAR 2023

- Played an integral role within a cross-functional team of five in the development of Recyclox, a decentralized token incentivizing individuals to deposit waste for recycling.
- Focused on testing the smart contract, collaborated closely with team members to collectively write and execute comprehensive test cases aimed at ensuring the robustness, security, and functionality of the contract.

EDUCATION

University Of Nigeria Nsukka, B.Sc Geology

Nigeria, Nsukka

2009 - 2014

PROJECTS

Bmi app.

Link Github

- User can select whether they want to use metric or imperial units
- Enter their height and weight
- See their BMI result, with their weight classification and healthy weight range
- View the optimal layout for the interface depending on their device's screen

TECHNOLOGIES

Stack

HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, React, React native, Next, Solidity, Git.

SOFT SKILL

Problem solving, Agile leadership,

LANGUAGES

Igbo native

• English,, fluent

size

See hover and focus states for all interactive elements on the page

Space tourism website.

Link Github

- This is a multipage website for space tourism
- Users can view the optimal layout for each of the website's pages depending on their device's screen size
- View each page and be able to toggle between the tabs to see new information

Recylox

Link Github

 The Recylox platform serves as a decentralized hub for distributing Recylox tokens to users who participate in plastic waste deposit activities. Through this platform, users can seamlessly engage in the token distribution process while contributing to environmental sustainability efforts.